{
    "subject": "resource/Ryan_Starr",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Ryan Starr is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9682357907295227,
            "question": "Is Ryan Starr from a specific state in the US?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9337714910507202,
            "question": "Is Ryan Starr American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7959778904914856,
            "question": "Where is Ryan Starr from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6510105133056641,
            "question": "Where was Ryan Starr born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6454741358757019,
            "question": "What country is Ryan Starr associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5695977210998535,
            "question": "What is Ryan Starr's place of origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5353482365608215,
            "question": "Ryan Starr might be known for something related to which country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4420158267021179,
            "question": "Can you tell me Ryan Starr's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42161232233047485,
            "question": "What is Ryan Starr's citizenship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28302663564682007,
            "question": "What can you tell me about Ryan Starr's home country?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ryan Starr is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8996_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Ryan Starr's citizenship?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8996_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me Ryan Starr's nationality?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8996_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ryan Starr might be known for something related to which country?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8996_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8996_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8996_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8996_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8996_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8996_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8996_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8996_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8996_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8996_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8996_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's the evaluation of the triple \"Ryan Starr is from United States\":\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that Ryan Starr was born in Sunland, California, USA (in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8996/re-ranker-msmarco/38.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8996/re-ranker-msmarco/49.txt), which indicates that she is from the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Ryan Starr was born in Sunland, California, USA, and have information about her being an American singer, actress, and television personality. This supports the statement that Ryan Starr is from the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}